Guide to the Newfield Public Library manuscript collection,1811-1965.
Newfield Public Library manuscript collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Newfield Public Library manuscript collection, 1811-1965.
3046
Newfield Public Library.
3 reels of microfilm.
Minutes, catalogues, records, proceedings, constitution, bylaws, a directory, a census book, a "death book," and periodicals.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes of the Newfield School Board, District 5, 8 and 18; Newfield Public Library minute book and catalogues, and Newfield Town Library Association, program; records and proceedings of the Town of Cayuta, Tioga County, New York; constitution, bylaws, and minutes of the Newfield Literary Society and Debating Club; constitution, by laws, minutes, and list of ex-presidents of the Newfield Ladies Monday Club; directory of the Newfield and Trumbull's Corners Methodist Episcopal Church and Sunday School; undertaker's census book and "Death Book" (annual list of people buried); Grant's Petersburg Progress (Virginia), Vol. l, No. 4, April 10, 1965; and issues of the Newfield Tribune and the Newfield Home News.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of the Newfield School Board, District 5, 8 and 18; Newfield Public Library minute book and catalogues, and Newfield Town Library Association, program; records and proceedings of the Town of Cayuta, Tioga County, New York; constitution, bylaws, and minutes of the Newfield Literary Society and Debating Club; constitution, by laws, minutes, and list of ex-presidents of the Newfield Ladies Monday Club; directory of the Newfield and Trumbull's Corners Methodist Episcopal Church and Sunday School; undertaker's census book and "Death Book" (annual list of people buried); Grant's Petersburg Progress (Virginia), Vol. l, No. 4, April 10, 1965; and issues of the Newfield Tribune and the Newfield Home News.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Newfield Public Library (N.Y.).; Newfield and Trumbull's Corners Methodist Episcopal Church Sunday School.; Newfield Ladies Monday Club (N.Y.); Newfield Literary Society and Debating Club (N.Y.); Newfield Town Library Association (N.Y.)
Titles:
Grant's Petersburg progress.; Newfield tribune.; Newfield home news.
Subjects:
Libraries--New York (State)--Newfield.; Women--Societies and clubs--New York (State)--Newfield.; School boards--New York (State)--Newfield.; Sunday schools--New York (State)--Newfield.
Places:
Tompkins County (N.Y.); Newfield (N.Y.); Tioga County (N.Y.); Cayuta (N.Y.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Newfield School Board Minutes
  - School District #8. October 4, 1831-October 13, 1868 (1855 not in order) (Reel 1)
  - School District #18. October 12, 1869-August 5, 1902 (1876 and 1886 missing) (Reel 1)
  - School District #5. August 3, 1897-August 1, 1905, August 4, 1908, May 5, 1925 (Reel 1)
- Newfield Public Library
  - Newfield Library Minute Book. June 24, 1889-December 3, 1900 (Reel 1)
  - Newfield Library Catalogues. 1892, 1899, 1901 (Reel 1)
  - Newfield Town Library Association, Programme. 1889 (Reel 1)
- Newfield Miscellaneous Items
  - The Records and Proceedings of the Town of Cayuta, Tioga County, New York 1811-1862. (Dates and type of entries not in consecutive order) (Reel 1)
  - Newfield Literary Society and Debating Club, Constitution and By-Laws, Minutes, October 17, 1896-April 23, 1897 (Reel 1)
  - Newfield Ladies Monday Club, Constitution and By-Laws, Minutes, October 11, 1948-March 15, 1965; list of Ex-Presidents, 1893-1947. (Reel 1)
  - Newfield and Trumbull's Corners Methodist Episcopal Church and Sunday School Directory, July 1, 1880 (Reel 1)
  - Census Book, A.R. Allen (Undertaker), 1898 (Reel 1)
  - "Death Book," A.R. Allen (Undertaker), 1903-1920 (Annual list of people buried) (Reel 1)
  - Grant's Petersburg Progress (Virginia) Vol. 1, No. 4, April 10, 1865 (Reel 1)
- Newfield Newspapers
  - Newfield Tribune. Vol. I April 21, 1888-April 13, 1889 (Reel 2)
  - Newfield Tribune. Vol. II April 20, 1889-April 12, 1890 (Reel 2)
  - Newfield Tribune. Vol. III April 19, 1890-June 28, 1890 (Reel 2)
  - Newfield Home News. June 7, 1941 (Sourvenir Edition) (with Vols. II and III) (Reel 2)